What should I do, Kotori?
I'm not so sure myself.
This is a bit unexpected.
Well, anime and manga characters
are ideal companions, in a way.
When you compare them to real people,
reality seems like a letdown.
Speaking from experience?
Tsk, tsk, tsk. I fancy
voice actresses, too, Commander.
Okay then.
Commander. Didn't Nia say
she liked some character?
Tokiya. Girls seem to love him.
I see...
Shido, help is on the way.
Just follow my plan to the word.
He's taking forever.
Strategizing with Kotori, maybe?
Oh, there you are--
It's Tokiya.
From Chronicle?
That costume's legit!
This seat's mine, woman.
Tokiya...? Why?
Mind yourself, woman.
I didn't say you can use my name.
Back off, woman.
Happiness climbing!
Sealing levels reached.
It worked, Shido! Go for it!
Huh? What's wrong?
Shut your mouth.
As if!
Eh?
Happiness falling!
It's lower than ever!
No way! Why?!
What the hell were you thinking?
Huh? Meaning?
Tokiya would never make moves
on a woman! Use common sense!
Common sense?
Tokiya's on a journey to avenge
his little sister and lover, Hibari!
As a lonely observer, I wouldn't dare
intrude on that beautiful world!
Don't break the fourth wall!
Don't break it!
Hey! Calm down, Nia!
Tokiya would never do that!
If you wanna make me fall for you,
come back when you're 2D!
Well, that didn't work out.
Oh my. You sure took a beating.
And who's fault is that?!
Commander. The plan failed,
but it's true that her levels rose.
Precisely.
In other words, if a character
she likes is brought to life,
it's possible to raise her happiness.
So, 2.5D will work.
In that case...!
Was that a bit cruel of me?
I guess ditching him there
wasn't the nicest thing.
Maybe I should've let him kiss me.
Though, Spirit power can't be sealed
unless you open your heart.
He seems like a good guy,
but 3D doesn't do it for me...
Argh! What the hell should I do?!
Just tell me, Raziel!
Huh?
Hello. Delivery.
"Demo"
"As thanks for your services,
we've sent you a demo of a new game."
Really? Have I done work
for this company before?
Looks like a school-based otome game.
"Please input your name..."
"Back | OK"
Nia... Honjo...
"Birthday: 2/29
Nia Honjo"
"Back | OK"
Hey, are you the new transfer student?
I'm Shido Itsuki. Nice to meet you.
He looks awfully like Boy...
Just a coincidence?
You're so funny, Nia.
Whoa! He spoke my name?!
And it sounded so natural, too!
Games sure have come far
in the past five years!
Next Saturday, huh?
Sure. Where should we go?
"Enter your date plans"
You're kidding! I can write anything?!
"I wanna buy doujinshi in Akiba"
There's no way this works.
Doujinshi in Akiba?
That's so like you. It's a date.
This dialogue! This freedom!
Are games really this advanced?!
Science is fricken' awesome!
Oh? You like these kinda books?
No, it's all good. I think
having passions is a wonderful thing.
She's played for two hours.
Happiness is rising steadily.
Once Nia's done with the game,
Shido can appear before her as "Itsuki."
Seeing how it's really him,
there's nothing to screw up.
Ah... Incredible!
But it's just a demo,
so I'll have to buy the real version.
Has this publisher made anything else?
I'll just ask Raziel.
Oh, shoot!
Huh?
Grr! This was all your doing?!
"Emergency Meeting"
"How to make Nia Honjo fall for Shido!?"
Well, now we've really pissed her off.
"Tohka Yatogami"
I'm not surprised. You guys used
a fake game to basically spy on her.
Hey, Shido. Why does Nia only like 2D?
"Kotori Itsuka"
Huh? Well...
I wondered that, too.
Reine is checking if
she had any manga artist pals.
Suggestion. Shouldn't we just
make Shido suit her preferences?
We're talking 2D, though.
Should we flatten him with a steamroller?
Eh?!
"Natsumi"
In that case, what if I made him
into a manga page with Haniel?
Hold your horses! Making me 2D is nuts!
"Origami Tobiichi"
I think Natsumi has the right idea.
Let's put Shido on a page.
"Emergency Meeting"
"How to make Nia Honjo fall for Shido!?"
--What?
--Huh?
Though, not by
transforming Shido himself,
but by making a manga
where Shido is a character.
Wha--?!
I see! That's a way of making him 2D!
"Yuzuru Yamai"
Mm! It'll be fine as long as
we write stuff that's true.
"Yoshino"
Yeah. If Nia knows about
everything Shido's done for us,
I'm sure she'll end up liking Shido, too.
Really, guys?
Ooh! Shido in a manga!
That's awesome! I wanna help!
Agreement. After tying in our 39th match,
"Best Manga Submission,"
the two of us are due
to put our skills back to the test.
You guys sure compete over everything.
The outside line? I wonder who it is?
Yo! Plotting something, are we?
I had Raziel tell me about this line...
and about what you're planning.
Still, even if you do make a manga,
why do you just assume that I'll read it?
I might've taken a look at it before,
but you guys have put me in "angry mode."
With Comico coming up,
I can't waste my time.
Comico? You're entering Comico?
Yup. My first in five years.
Miku, what's Comico?
Comic Colosseum.
It's a convention for people
to sell the doujinshi they make.
If our manga was worth reading,
would you take the time to read it?
Hmm?
For example, if our manga manages
to sell more copies than yours at Comico.
Oh? You're actually serious?
Yeah. If we end up winning,
you have to read our manga.
Okay! You're on!
You think you can beat
Souji Honjo, do you?
H-Hey, Kotori...
Don't worry. I've got a plan.
They underestimate me.
They really think they can beat a pro?
Regardless of what happens, it's not like
I could like a real person anyway.
Besides, it's not like
anyone would like me, either.
That's the all-knowing Angel,
Raziel, is it not?
Nice to meet you, Nia Honjo.
My name is Kurumi Tokisaki.
Kurumi Tokisaki,
the Spirit who manipulates time...
I see. You're the one
who saved me from DEM.
That saves an explanation.
You're the second Spirit
seen after the "Spirit of Origin."
I've been longing to meet you.
Hmm? And why's that?
No need to be on your guard.
I just came to ask a favor.
Could you look into something with Raziel?
Tell me about the Spirit of Origin...
...and how to kill it.
Whoa! This is neat!
It's so "professional."
Comico's in two days.
Can we do it in time?
We'll have to.
Let's see how well everyone draws.
You draw something, too.
Me?
Didn't you use to sketch all the time?
The Black Knight, Lievan, or something?
"The Black Knight, Lievan"
If you're done drawing, let's see it!
I see... Yeah, very cute.
Really?!
Yeah, but I don't think
it'll work for us this time.
Oh...
S-Sorry.
Next one! Next!
No fair, Darling!
Whoa! You guys are pretty good!
So far, you two are our
best candidates. So, who's next?
What did you draw, Origami?!
Shido and me, becoming one.
No one asked you to draw that!
If we're trying to sell doujinshi,
going 18+ is the way to go.
We're entering as
a "General Audience" booth, you know.
What's up? If you drew something,
let's see it. C'mon.
Um, it's bad, so don't expect much.
I didn't sleep well last night,
and I haven't drawn in forever.
Okay, fine. Just show us already!
Incredible, Natsumi!
Who knew you had such skill?!
Well, I wouldn't say "skill."
But I did imitate
a manga artist once, just for fun.
That settles it!
Natsumi's our main artist.
With Yuzuru, Kaguya, Shido,
and Origami supporting her.
Roger that!
A-Are you really fine with me?
Of course! We need your talent
to help Nia, Natsumi!
Don't complain about it later.
Kotori, what can the rest of us do?
I have another job for you guys.
In a way, it's more important
than the manga.
Hmm?
Well then...
That's troubling news.
What do you suppose we do?
Indeed. According to what
Raziel had to say,
even if I gather Spirit power, I stand
no chance against the Spirit of Origin.
But...
...what does it matter anyway?
I'm the Spirit with power over time.
The notion of time makes
everything else insignificant.
Gah! Messed up the grid.
Geh! The tears are invading the white!
Likewise. The ink spread under the ruler.
It's okay. This can be fixed.
Shido, got a minute?
I'm Hiroki Takajo.
The manga artist!
Yes. Looking into Nia's--that is,
Souji Honjo's friends, led me to her.
I hear you guys are relatives of Honjo's?
Yeah. We're worried since
we're having trouble contacting Nia.
So, we're hoping you can share
anything you know about her.
Honestly, I've been
worried about her, too.
I was glad to hear that
she's back to making manga,
but since it seems that she
doesn't like me, I'm not sure I can help.
--Huh?
At one time, she and I
used to get along well.
But then she suddenly acted cold
and we drifted apart.
Perhaps I did something rude
to her without knowing.
Honjo is a kind and friendly person,
but as for her life before an artist...
She rarely spoke about
the friends she had in the past.
And I feel like she suddenly distances
herself from any friends in the making.
If only I knew what I did to upset her,
I'd take that chance to apologize, but...
I bet Raziel played a part in this.
If you had the power to know anything,
you'd look up those around you.
True...
That probably made Nia
unable to trust other people.
Everyone's said or done mean things
behind people's backs to some extent.
You'd realize how
pathetic people are in no time.
She only opens her heart to 2D
because she knows they won't betray her.
That's--
--You think that's all it is?
--Huh?
Raziel shows her people's dark side.
But knowing Nia's personality,
I feel like she'd look past that.
Anyway, let's focus on the doujinshi.
We need another chance to talk with Nia.
Without that, we'll get nowhere.
Finally! Page 57 is done!
I just finished 58, too.
I, whom only hurricanes can subdue,
have finished the last page!
"Don't worry about it. Besides, we'd have
been in trouble if you hadn't come."
"Hey, Natsumi."
Gather. I'll scan all our pages
and make it digital.
With editing and printing,
it's gonna be a close one.
Good work, Shido.
You look exhausted, too.
What have you been up to?
It's a secret, Shido.
Look forward to it.
Are you okay, Natsumi?
Natsumi, how about a break?
Oh, right.
Swap out. You've been working non-stop.
No, it's fine. I'm almost done.
You did the storyboard, draft,
and worked harder than anyone.
That's right. The convention is
the real battle. Leave the rest to us.
Agreed. You've worked
way too hard, Natsumi.
Rest is important, too.
It's okay. I won't be
that much use at the convention.
This is about all I can do, so...
But...
You see, I'm really glad
I was saved by all of you guys.
This time, I can do my part
to help another Spirit.
That really... really makes me happy.
So, this is nothing.
I wanna show that dummy Nia, too:
That friends are a wonderful thing.
"H-Hey, Natsumi?"
And that's... the last... one.
Natsumi?!
Good work, Natsumi.
"Dummies..."
"*W-Waaah*"
"H-Hey, Natsumi?"
Now we have our weapon.
Guys, we've gotta win, no matter what!
"Episode 02:
'So Be It! 2D It Is!'"
Now then, shall we begin our date?
The doujinshi convention
is a battle of passion!
The love and fervor of artists
heats up the winter cold!
Next time: "What's Yours Is Mine."
"Episode 03: 'What's Yours Is Mine.'"
Westcott's intentions are finally known.